Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.1.3.2
  - Subject files: Photographs found among Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas's papers, circa 1917 - 1918; 9 (Box 1513)
    - Verso: They saw our machine here and sent some fire over but it didn't come very close, 6-verso
    - I was trying to see what the inside of a dugout looked like, 7
    - Verso: I was trying to see what the inside of a dugout looked like, 7-verso
    - [Mrs. Thomas trying to look inside of a dugout], 8
    - Capt. Tozzi Capt. Lord Stanley Prince of Wales - Capt. Larking and inc. Taken in front of Doges Palace - Venice, 9
    - Verso: Capt. Tozzi Capt. Lord Stanley Prince of Wales - Capt. Larking and inc. Taken in front of Doges Palace - Venice, 9-verso
    - Madame Tetrazzini and the Thomas family after taking a spin in the Villa Borghese in her lovely car, 10
    - Verso: Madame Tetrazzini and the Thomas family after taking a spin in the Villa Borghese in her lovely car, 10-verso
    - Tetrazzini and the Thomases - Rome, 11
    - Verso: Tetrazzini and the Thomases - Rome, 11-verso
    - Discussing ways of helping war refugees; Capt. Tozzi, my wife, Capt. Thomas, Mrs. Crabites, 12
    - Verso: Discussing ways of helping war refugees; Capt. Tozzi, my wife, Capt. Thomas, Mrs. Crabites, 12-verso
    - A fountain in the court of St. Peters, with the Vatican in the background, 13
    - Verso: A fountain in the court of St. Peters, with the Vatican in the background, 13-verso
    - Denver's world-famous juvenile judge lecturing one of his proteges whom he found wandering in the streets of Rome., 14
    - Verso: Denver's world-famous juvenile judge lecturing one of his proteges whom he found wandering in the streets of Rome., 14-verso
    - In Pisa by the Leaning Tower Miss Flannini with me., 15
    - Verso: In Pisa by the Leaning Tower Miss Flannini with me., 15-verso
    - The famous "Rialto" where Antonio bargained with Shylock., 16
    - Verso: The famous "Rialto" where Antonio bargained with Shylock., 16-verso
    - I had the time of my life in Venice. I love riding in gondolas., 17
    - Verso: I had the time of my life in Venice. I love riding in gondolas., 17-verso
    - [Mrs. Thomas sitting with two military men], 18
    - [Mrs. Thomas and two men having tea], 19
    - [Mrs. Thomas and three men with dog], 20
    - [Mrs. Thomas talking to a military man], 21
    - [Mrs. Thomas talking to a military man], 22
    - [Mrs. Thomas and a man in military uniform], 23
    - [Run-down building], 24
    - [Field full of military men], 25
    - Neuilly Hospital, 26
    - Verso: Neuilly Hospital, 26-verso
    - Mr. Thomas with two French orphans, 27
    - Verso: Mr. Thomas with two French orphans, 27-verso
    - A typical Paris "newsboy". In front of the Church of the Madeline. Lowell Thomas, 28
    - Verso: A typical Paris "newsboy". In front of the Church of the Madeline. Lowell Thomas, 28-verso
    - A few miles from Paris, 29
    - Verso: A few miles from Paris, 29-verso
    - The Grand Opera House. To the left is a famous cafe (Cafe de La Paix), 30
    - Verso: The Grand Opera House. To the left is a famous cafe (Cafe de La Paix), 30-verso
  - Subject files: Prince of Wales, 1917; 10 (Box 1513)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lord Stanley, The Prince of Whales, and a British Commander in St. Mark's Square, Venice], 1
    - Lord Stanley, Yours Truly, The Prince of Wales, and a British Naval commander, in St. Mark's Square, Venice, 2
    - Verso: Lord Stanley, Yours Truly, The Prince of Wales, and a British Naval commander, in St. Mark's Square, Venice, 2-verso
    - Note: L.T. and His Royal Highness, the Prince of Wales (hand on hip), during the war, 3
    - L.T. with his back to the camera, and the Prince of Wales (with the cane and hand on waist) in St. Mark's Square, Venice, when the Queen City of the Adriatic was deserted, with the Austrian army only fourteen miles away., 4
    - Verso: L.T. with his back to the camera, and the Prince of Wales (with the cane and hand on waist) in St. Mark's Square, Venice, when the Queen City of the Adriatic was deserted, with the Austrian army only fourteen miles away., 4-verso
    - Note: St. Mark's Venice. Prince of Wales - cane LT - back to camera 1917, 5
    - Tiffany. Left to right: - Yours truly, Capt. Tozzi of the Italian army assigned to accompany me by the Minister of War, Lord Stanley, The Prince of Wales, and a British Naval Commander in front of the Doge's Palace in VeniceT, 6
    - Verso: Tiffany. Left to right: - Yours truly, Capt. Tozzi of the Italian army assigned to accompany me by the Minister of War, Lord Stanley, The Prince of Wales, and a British Naval Commander in front of the Doge's Palace in Venice, 6-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lord Stanley, The Prince of Whales, and a British Commander in St. Mark's Square, Venice], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lord Stanley, The Prince of Whales, and a British Commander talking in St. Mark's Square, Venice], 8
  - Subject files: Serbian front, 1917; 11 (Box 1513)
    - L.T. (center) at American Red Cross headquarters on the Serbian front, 1
    - Note: L.T. (center) at American Red Cross headquarters on the Serbian front, 2
    - Note: L.T. interviewing the Premier of Serbia during the early days of World War I; 1917, 3
    - L.T. interviewing the Premier of Serbia during the early days of World War I; 1917, 4
  - Subject files: Harry G. Thomas, circa 1917 - 1918; 12 (Box 1513)
    - Postcard - Col. H. G. Thomas holding cane with fellow doctors in London at the General Hospital - World War One, 1
    - Note: H. G. Thomas holding cane with fellow doctors in London at the General Hospital - World War One, 2
    - Postcard, 3
    - Postcard - 7 Stablefird Highcrops Hamlet Rd. Walasey. N. Liverpool (Address), 4
    - Verso: Postcard - 7 Stablefird Highcrops Hamlet Rd. Walasey. N. Liverpool (Address), 4-verso
    - [Two men and a woman talking (location?)], 5
    - [Medical center in (location?)], 6
    - [Portrait of Harry G. Thomas (?)], 7
    - [Portrait of Harry G. Thomas (?)], 8
    - [Portrait of Harry G. Thomas (?)], 9
    - [Portrait of Harry G. Thomas (?)], 10
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas, 1971 - 1976; 13 (Box 1513)
    - It has taken Lowell Thomas 51 years of broadcasting, many more in public speaking, scores of files and 52 books to tell the things has seen and done from Allenby at Jerusalem and Lawrence in Arabia to Shangria and Timbuktu with thousands of points in between. Thomas is shown during interview with UPI 5/7. In background is a painting of (T.E.) Lawrence in Arabia; Please credit United Press International Photo, 1
    - Verso: It has taken Lowell Thomas 51 years of broadcasting, many more in public speaking, scores of files and 52 books to tell the things has seen and done from Allenby at Jerusalem and Lawrence in Arabia to Shangria and Timbuktu with thousands of points in between. Thomas is shown during interview with UPI 5/7. In background is a painting of (T.E.) Lawrence in Arabia; Please credit United Press International Photo, 1-verso
    - Lowell for the man of the trees, 2
    - The Boys' Life of Colonel Lawrence by Lowell Thomas, 3
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1917 - 1919; 14 (Box 1513)
    - [Lowell Thomas accompanying Frances Ryan Thomas and one other], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas and one other], 2
    - Essad Pasha, Dictator of Albania, and L.T., 3
    - Verso: Essad Pasha, Dictator of Albania, and L.T., 3-verso
    - Mr. Thomas and President of Albania, 4
    - Verso: Mr. Thomas and President of Albania, 4-verso
    - Essed Pasha, former President of Albania at Salonica, 5
    - Verso: Essed Pasha, former President of Albania at Salonica, 5-verso
    - Essed Pashah, murdered "President of Albania" and L.T., 6
    - Verso: Essed Pashah, murdered "President of Albania" and L.T., 6-verso
    - [Essed Pashah, murdered "President of Albania" and Lowell Thomas], 7
    - [Essed Pashah, murdered "President of Albania" and Lowell Thomas], 8
    - Dec. 1917 - Lowell Thomas, 9
    - Verso: Dec. 1917 - Lowell Thomas, 9-verso
    - [December 1917-Lowell Thomas], 10
    - [December 1917-Lowell Thomas], 11
    - Lowell Thomas while filming the operations of Allenby's Cavalry, during WWI, during war against the Turks in Holy Land, 12
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas while filming the operations of Allenby's Cavalry, during WWI, during war against the Turks in Holy Land, 12-verso
    - Note: Lowell Thomas while filming the operations of General Allenby's cavalry, during WWI, during war against the Turks in Holy Land, 13
    - Mrs. Thomas [next to airplane], 14
    - Verso: Mrs. Thomas, 14-verso
    - L.T. mounted on a pure Arab, while with Lawrence in the Arabian Desert, 15
    - Verso: L.T. mounted on a pure Arab, while with Lawrence in the Arabian Desert, 15-verso
    - Lowell Thomas on a pure Arab in the Arab Revolt, 16
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas on a pure Arab in the Arab Revolt, 16-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and 2 orphans in the battle zone during war. Their parents had been killed and they were being taken care of by American soldiers in St. Mihiel], 17
    - L.T. and 2 orphans in the battle zone during war. Their parents had been killed and they were being taken care of by Amer. soldiers in St. Mihiel, 18
    - Verso: L.T. and 2 orphans in the battle zone during war. Their parents had been killed and they were being taken care of by Amer. soldiers in St. Mihiel, 18-verso
    - Mr. Thomas and 2 children in France, 19
    - Verso: Mr. Thomas and 2 children in France, 19-verso
    - L.T. and two refugee children, 20
    - Note: L.T. and two refugee children, 21
    - L.T. and two refugee children, 22
    - Note: L.T. and two refugee children, 23
    - [Lowell Thomas and two refugee children], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas and two refugee children], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and two orphans], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas and two orphans], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas mounted on a pure Arab in the Arabian Desert], 28
    - On the beach., 29
    - Verso: On the beach., 29-verso
    - L.T. visiting the famous "Hat in the Ring" squadron. When Capt. Eddie Rickenbacker's outfit was fighting in the air over St. Mihiel, Toul and Verdun, in World War I, 30
    - Note: L.T. visiting the famous "Hat in the Ring" squadron. When Capt. Eddie Rickenbacker's outfit was fighting in the air over St. Mihiel, Toul and Verdun, in World War I, 31
    - L.T. on the right, accompanied by Flying Officer Lieutenant Tommy Ward, enjoying a vacation at Chateau Valoncey, castle of the Duke de Talleyrand, Napoleon's Prime Minister; Signal Corps A.E.F.; U.S. Army Photographic Laboratory, 32
    - Note: L.T. on the right, accompanied by Flying Officer Lieutenant Tommy Ward, enjoying a vacation at Chateau Valoncey, castle of the Duke de Talleyrand, Napoleon's Prime Minister; Signal Corps A.E.F.; U.S. Army Photographic Laboratory, 33
    - Mary Gladwin, nurse. Mrs. T., 34
    - Verso: Mary Gladwin, nurse. Mrs. T., 34-verso
    - cap: - black visor, gold trimming, scarlet top. Cape and coat: - bright king's blue. Grey hair and mustache; Foch? Joffre and L.T. A.E.F. passed as censored; 8 Nov 1917, 35
    - Verso: cap: - black visor, gold trimming, scarlet top. Cape and coat: - bright king's blue. Grey hair and mustache; Foch? Joffre and L.T. A.E.F. passed as censored; 8 Nov 1917, 35-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and his moving picture camera], 36
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to man in an arm sling], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to man in an arm sling], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to man in an arm sling], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to man in an arm sling], 40
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a young child], 41
    - [Lowell Thomas looking off a ship deck], 42
    - L.T. and his chief cameraman, Mr. Harry Chase, discussing the evanescence of life and the rapidity of change in this old world; with the Parthenon for a background. This picture was taken on the summit of the Acropolis above the city of Athens. WWI, 43
    - Note: L.T. and his chief cameraman, Mr. Harry Chase, discussing the evanescence of life and the rapidity of change in this old world; with the Parthenon for a background. This picture was taken on the summit of the Acropolis above the city of Athens. WWI, 44
    - Frances Thomas wearing helmet. GERMANY OF TODAY. Parade helmet of the Kaiser - taken by a Spartacus soldier during the riot in the Kaiser's Palace, when all of his uniforms were taken by the soldiers. Lowell Thomas, American War Correspondent, was quickly on the spot and bought this interesting souvenir from the soldier and brought it with him to New York, 45
    - Verso: Frances Thomas wearing helmet. GERMANY OF TODAY. Parade helmet of the Kaiser - taken by a Spartacus soldier during the riot in the Kaiser's Palace, when all of his uniforms were taken by the soldiers. Lowell Thomas, American War Correspondent, was quickly on the spot and bought this interesting souvenir from the soldier and brought it with him to New York, 45-verso
    - Mrs. Thomas, wife of the correspondent, wearing the Kaiser's helmet which Mr. Thomas brought back to America, 46
    - Verso: Mrs. Thomas, wife of the correspondent, wearing the Kaiser's helmet which Mr. Thomas brought back to America, 46-verso
    - The Kaiser's helmet worn by an American woman, 47
    - Verso: The Kaiser's helmet worn by an American woman, 47-verso
    - The Kaiser's helmet worn by an American woman, 48
    - Verso: The Kaiser's helmet worn by an American woman, 48-verso
    - The Ideal Septim, French Mlli V.D. Gaudel [?]; Miss Ackard W.W.C.D. Miss Slate, 49
    - Verso: The Ideal Septim, French Mlli V.D. Gaudel [?]; Miss Ackard W.W.C.D. Miss Slate, 49-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with nurse Mary Gladwin and one other], 50
    - [The Kaiser's helmet worn by an American woman], 51
    - [American woman wearing the Kaiser's helmet], 52
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas - Italy, 1917 - 1918; 15 (Box 1513)
    - Mr. Thomas on sled in Alps, 1
    - Verso: Mr. Thomas on sled in Alps, 1-verso
    - [Mr. Thomas on sled in Alps], 2
    - Verso: J. Horace Mcfarland Co., Harrisburg, PA, 2-verso
    - [Mr. Thomas on sled in Alps], 3
    - Verso: J. Horace Mcfarland Co., Harrisburg, PA, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas on dog sled in the Alps], 4
    - Verso: Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas on dog sled in the Alps], 5
    - L.T. with his ubiquitous Stetson hat, looking up at one of the huge protector pads hanging before one of the exquisitely carved entrances on the Cathedral of St. Mark's, in Venice. Great precautions were taken to protect these priceless treasures, which were in constant danger from exploding aerial bombs, 6
    - Note: L.T. with his ubiquitous Stetson hat, looking up at one of the huge protector pads hanging before one of the exquisitely carved entrances on the Cathedral of St. Mark's, in Venice. Great precautions were taken to protect these priceless treasures, which were in constant danger from exploding aerial bombs, 7
    - Luisa Tetrazzini, Lowell and Frances Thomas, 8
    - Verso: Luisa Tetrazzini, Lowell and Frances Thomas, 8-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and Capt Tozzi, who formerly was the Italian military attache of the American traveloguer and now is on Premier Orlando's personal staff; Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica, 9
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and Capt Tozzi, who formerly was the Italian military attache of the American traveloguer and now is on Premier Orlando's personal staff; Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica, 9-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and Captain Tozzi], 10
    - Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica; L.T. and Piero Tozzi, 11
    - Verso: Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica; L.T. and Piero Tozzi, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and Piero Tozzi], 12
    - Verso: Comando Supremo Censura Fotografica, 12-verso
    - Mrs. Thomas and Piero Tozzi, 13
    - Verso: Mrs. Thomas and Piero Tozzi, 13-verso
    - Mrs. Thomas and Harry G. Thomas, 14
    - Verso: Mrs. Thomas and Harry G. Thomas, 14-verso
    - In the jungles near Naples. Fran pointing out a lion in a nearby tree; Mrs. Thomas and Harry G. Thomas, 15
    - Verso: In the jungles near Naples. Fran pointing out a lion in a nearby tree; Mrs. Thomas and Harry G. Thomas, 15-verso
    - A tea party in the Villa Borghese - Rome; Lowell Thomas, Frances Thomas, Piero Tozzi and Harry G. Thomas, 16
    - Verso: A tea party in the Villa Borghese - Rome; Lowell Thomas, Frances Thomas, Piero Tozzi and Harry G. Thomas, 16-verso
    - L.T. and wife in Rome. She with the Amer. Red Cross, 17
    - Verso: Life in the trenches; Mrs. Thomas, 17-verso
    - Note: L.T. and wife in Rome. She with the Amer. Red Cross, 18
    - Lowell - uniform - Frances Thomas - Red Cross uniform of 1st World War, 19
    - Verso: Lowell - uniform - Frances Thomas - Red Cross uniform of 1st World War, 19-verso
    - The happy family. Come have some ice cream with us. Rome - June 1918 [Lowell and Frances Thomas], 20
    - Verso: The happy family. Come have some ice cream with us. Rome - June 1918 [Lowell and Frances Thomas], 20-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 21
    - The horrors of war [Harry G. Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas], 22
    - Verso: The horrors of war [Harry G. Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas], 22-verso
    - Captain H.G. Thomas, of Victor, Colorado, treating a well known Red Cross nurse [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] to a dish of Italian Hokey Poky. Tommy, 23
    - Verso: Captain H.G. Thomas, of Victor, Colorado, treating a well known Red Cross nurse [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] to a dish of Italian Hokey Poky. Tommy, 23-verso
    - Mrs. T. amid ruins, 24
    - Verso: Mrs. T. amid ruins, 24-verso
    - Portrait of a peg-legged sailor [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] crossing a "Strada" in Naples. Tommy, 25
    - Verso: Portrait of a peg-legged sailor [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] crossing a "Strada" in Naples. Tommy, 25-verso
    - How do you like my looks? I think I look pretty rackish (on the way to front) Venice, 26
    - Verso: How do you like my looks? I think I look pretty rackish (on the way to front) Venice, 26-verso
    - Frances Thomas in Red Cross uniform, 27
    - Verso: Frances Thomas in Red Cross uniform, 27-verso
    - Frances Thomas in Red Cross uniform, 28
    - St. Mark's in the back. It is beautiful. Venice looks quite deserted but now the people are returning since the last victory. The favorite stunt is to leave drinks or coffee, in the square., 29
    - Verso: St. Mark's in the back. It is beautiful. Venice looks quite deserted but now the people are returning since the last victory. The favorite stunt is to leave drinks or coffee, in the square., 29-verso
    - Frances Thomas in Red Cross uniform, 30
    - Feeding the pigeons in St. Mark's Square - Venice., 31
    - Verso: Feeding the pigeons in St. Mark's Square - Venice., 31-verso
    - [Frances Thomas wearing wartime head-gear], 32
    - How do you like my wartime head-gear?, 33
    - Verso: How do you like my wartime head-gear?, 33-verso
    - How do you like my war headgear? Starting for the Lower Piave from Venice, July 1st 1918, 34
    - Verso: How do you like my war headgear? Starting for the Lower Piave from Venice, July 1st 1918, 34-verso
    - Frances Ryan Thomas heading to the front, crossing the Piave River, 35
    - Frances Ryan Thomas heading to the front, crossing the Piave River, 36
    - Frances Ryan Thomas heading to the front, crossing the Piave River, 37
    - Frances Ryan Thomas heading to the front, crossing the Piave River, 38
    - Frances Ryan Thomas heading to the front, crossing the Piave River, 39
  Box 1514
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.1.3.2
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas - Italy, 1917 - 1918; 1 (Box 1514)
    - Lowell and Frances Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Harry G. Thomas, 1
    - Verso: Lowell and Frances Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Harry G. Thomas, 1-verso
    - Lowell and Frances Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Piero Tozzi, Luisa Tetrazzini, 2
    - Verso: Lowell and Frances Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Piero Tozzi, Luisa Tetrazzini, 2-verso
    - Lowell and Frances Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, 3
    - Verso: Lowell and Frances Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, 3-verso
    - Piero Tozzi, Harry G. Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Frances Thomas, 4
    - Verso: Piero Tozzi, Harry G. Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Frances Thomas, 4-verso
    - Lowell and Frances Thomas, Piero Tozzi, Harry G. Thomas, 5
    - Verso: Lowell and Frances Thomas, Piero Tozzi, Harry G. Thomas, 5-verso
    - Verso: Piero Tozzi, Frances Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Harry G. Thomas, 6
    - Piero Tozzi, Frances Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Luisa Tetrazzini, Harry G. Thomas, 6-verso
    - Major Tozzi and Frances Thomas, St. Marks, 7
    - Verso: Major Tozzi and Frances Thomas, St. Marks, 7-verso
    - Luisa Tetrazzini, Frances Thomas, 8
    - Verso: Luisa Tetrazzini, Frances Thomas, 8-verso
    - Captain H. G. Thomas, of the Christopher Colombo Hospital, Genoa, Italy, and his son "Lowell" taking a well known one-legged Red Cross worker[Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] for a stroll in the Piazza at St. Peters - Tommy, 9
    - Verso: Captain H. G. Thomas, of the Christopher Colombo Hospital, Genoa, Italy, and his son "Lowell" taking a well known one-legged Red Cross worker[Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas] for a stroll in the Piazza at St. Peters - Tommy, 9-verso
    - Harry G. Thomas, Frances Thomas, 10
    - Verso: Harry G. Thomas, Frances Thomas, 10-verso
    - Harry G. Thomas, Frances and Lowell Thomas, 11
    - Verso: Harry G. Thomas, Frances and Lowell Thomas, 11-verso
    - Frances Thomas, Prince of Wales, 12
    - Verso: Frances Thomas, Prince of Wales, 12-verso
    - Frances Thomas, St. Peter's square, 13
    - Verso: Frances Thomas, St. Peter's square, 13-verso
    - Frances Thomas, 14
    - Verso: Frances Thomas, 14-verso
    - Frances Thomas, Piave Front, 15
    - Verso: Frances Thomas, Piave Front, 15-verso
    - L.T. and Major Tozzi, 16
    - Verso: L.T. and Major Tozzi, 16-verso
    - Here's where I got lost "without a drop to drink", 17
    - Verso: Here's where I got lost "without a drop to drink", 17-verso
    - [People gathered by Hindenburg statue], 18
  - Subject Files: Miscellaneous photographs, circa 1917 - 1919; 2 (Box 1514)
    - Signal corps A.E.F.; U.S. Army Photographic Laboratory. L. Thomas, 1
    - Verso: Signal corps A.E.F.; U.S. Army Photographic Laboratory. L. Thomas, 1-verso
    - Neuilly Hospital, near Paris. Left to right: 1. [no entry] 2. R.P. Lamont Jr. 3. Thomsen, 2
    - Verso: Neuilly Hospital, near Paris. Left to right: 1. [no entry] 2. R.P. Lamont Jr. 3. Thomsen, 2-verso
    - A group of American women who are working in France. The cross is over Mrs. Vanderbilt's head; A.E.F. passed as censored; 7 Nov 1917, 3
    - Verso: A group of American women who are working in France. The cross is over Mrs. Vanderbilt's head; A.E.F. passed as censored; 7 Nov 1917, 3-verso
    - Ruine d'un vieux Chateau situe entre D. Brod et Humpoletz; 27/X/23, 4
    - Verso: Ruine d'un vieux Chateau situe entre D. Brod et Humpoletz; 27/X/23, 4-verso
    - Interior of church wrecked by German shell fire. It took the sixty-first Regiment Infantry two days to capture a machine gun nest in the tower. Aincreville, Meuse, France. November 4, 1918, 5
    - Verso: Interior of church wrecked by German shell fire. It took the sixty-first Regiment Infantry two days to capture a machine gun nest in the tower. Aincreville, Meuse, France. November 4, 1918, 5-verso
    - General Quinquondon, who assisted Marshall Joffre in Battle of the Marne; A.E.F. passed as censored; 7 Nov 1917, 6
    - Verso: General Quinquondon, who assisted Marshall Joffre in Battle of the Marne; A.E.F. passed as censored; 7 Nov 1917, 6-verso
    - Samuel Woodfill whom Pershing called "the greatest American soldier of the war.", 7